rkguns.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy : RK Guns

We appreciate the trust our customers have placed in Rural King for more than 55 years, and we are committed to respecting your privacy rights and personal information. This Privacy Policy, last updated on September 24, 2015, describes the information RK Internet, LLC (“we” or “our”) collects from visitors to our website, www.rkguns.com (“Website”) and from Website and Rural King store customers (visitors and customers are referred to in this Privacy Policy as “you” or “your”) and it explains how we use that information.

**CONTENTS**

  * Information we collect from you
  * How we use the information we collect
  * Information we share with others and your privacy rights
  * Your choices about how we communicate with you
  * Cookies and pixel tags
  * Your email and how we use it
  * Links to third party websites
  * Reviewing and updating your information
  * Privacy of children
  * Security
  * Changes to this Privacy Policy
  * Customer service
  * Contact us

**Information we collect from you**

We may collect information (including your name, address, telephone number, email address, device location, transaction information, credit card information, and/or your birthday, individually and collectively “Information”) from you in any or all of the following ways: when you place an order on our Website, when you make a purchase at a Rural King store (although we do not require personal information such as your name, address, or telephone number as a condition to accepting payment by a credit card or debit card), when you apply for a license for hunting, fishing, or firearms, when you view products on our Website, when you return or exchange any item you purchase, receive a gift package, create an account on the Website, sign up for email updates, or enter a contest or sweepstakes we sponsor, when you are referred to us through a marketing promotion or by another customer, when you participate in a marketing survey, promotion or event, or when you obtain or maintain a Rural King credit card or account.  
We maintain Information, along with a record of your purchases, any exchanges or returns, and the redemption of any gift certificates or coupons, in a secure database. We may combine the Information with other data and information we receive about you from third parties. We also gather information about how visitors navigate through our Website by using click stream data gathered with “cookies” and other online tools such as “pixel tags”.

**How we use the Information we collect**

To continue the outstanding service Rural King has provided its customers for more than 55 years, we collect Information that allows us to deliver the best possible customer experience, and we use that Information to process and track your online orders and purchases, to provide any services that you request or that are used to fulfill an order (including shipping, delivery and setup options that are provided by third parties), to send you promotional offers we believe will be of interest to you or to your family, to send you email updates, to identify your product and service preferences, to customize communications with you, to provide information concerning product recalls of any products you have purchased, to improve or expand the selection of products we offer, and to enhance the level of customer service we provide.

 **Information we share with others and your privacy rights  
**  
We contract with third parties to provide certain services to our customers, which include, or may include, shipping, name and address confirmation, email distribution, third party advertising, management of promotions, market research, and payment processing. We provide such third parties only the information they require to perform their contracted services, and we establish and maintain our business relationships with each based upon the requirement that your privacy is respected and protected. From time to time we may make our customer list (names and addresses) and general shopping activity available to third parties whose products or services we believe will be of interest to you, provided that each such third party agrees to respect and protect your privacy as we do. We do not share email addresses for this purpose. If you do not want to receive mailings from any third party and prefer that we not share any of your Information with any third party, please unsubscribe to opt out. In some circumstances, where we are required to do so by law or by court order, we may disclose Information to a government agency, and we may also provide Information to third parties offering fraud protection or identity theft services. We also reserve the right, as we deem necessary, to use Information to protect the rights, property, and safety of our stores, our company, our customers, our employees or others, and to prevent harm or loss in connection with any suspected or actual unlawful activity.

 **Your choices about how we communicate with you  
**  
You may choose the type of information you receive from us. If you prefer not to receive mailings or email updates from us, please contact us at our address below. You can also unsubscribe from our email updates by using the link provided at the bottom of each email message we send you.  
If you do not want to receive email or mailed communications from us, please write to us at the following address, making sure that you provide us with your exact name and address, or use the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of your e-mail:

RK Internet LLC, Attention: Customer Service   
4216 Dewitt Avenue  
Mattoon, Illinois 61938

Because we plan our mailed communications in advance, it may take several weeks for you to stop receiving mailings from us.

 **Cookies and pixel tags  
**  
We use “cookies”, small data files stored by your computer’s web browser, to help you place an order on our Website. We also use cookies to enhance and personalize your online shopping experience. We use cookies to remember what items you put into your shopping cart, to recognize when you return to the Website, to speed up your checkout, if you have established an online account, to determine how visitors and customer navigate through the Website, which products visitors and customers request in searches, and to develop and deliver personalized marketing. If you choose to disable cookies, you may order by telephoning us at 1-844-754-8671 from 7 a.m. to 5 p.m. Central time, Monday through Friday.  
We also use pixel tags, tiny graphic images, to tell us what parts of our Website you visited and to measure the effectiveness of searches you may choose to make on the Website. Pixel tags also let us send you emails in a format you can read, and they let us know when you have opened an email message from us.

**Your email and how we use it  
**  
If you provide your email address, we will use it to communicate with you, as necessary regarding any order, return or refund, to respond to any request from you, and to provide customer service. When you place an online order through the Website, you will receive an email confirmation of the order, and, in most cases, package or shipment tracking information  
We may also use your email to send you informational and promotional emails about products, services, special offers, sweepstakes and drawings, or events that we believe will be of interest to you. If you no longer wish to receive emails from us, please click the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of your e-mail. We ask that you allow us a minimum of ten (10) days from the time you make this election to implement your request. Even if you decide to opt out of receiving future email communications, we may still contact you to respond to an inquiry, to confirm an order and its status, to communicate regarding product recalls, warranties, or service agreements, or if required by any law or regulation or any court order. 

**Links to third party websites  
**  
We may elect, from time to time, to offer links from our Website to other third party websites. Because we do not control the content of third party websites, we are not responsible for, and we make no guarantees concerning, the accuracy, currency, suitability, or quality of the information in such content. We assume no responsibility for objectionable, inaccurate, misleading, or unlawful content made available by any third party on its website, nor do we assume any responsibility or liability for products, materials, or practices (including the privacy policies) of such websites. We strongly encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party website carefully.

**Reviewing and updating your information  
**  
You may review and update any of the information you have provided us by logging into the “My Account” section of the Website using your registered email address and password.

 **Privacy of children  
**  
Our Website is not intended for, or directed to, children. We do not knowingly collect or maintain any Information relating to children under the age of 13, without express parental consent. If you are a parent or guardian and believe we have unauthorized Information relating to a child, please contact us at 1-844-754-8671.

**Security  
**  
We use security measures consistent with retail practices to protect Information and online transactions through our Website. Our Websites uses encryption technology, including Secure Sockets Layer, to protect the information we transmit across the Internet.

 **Privacy Policy changes  
**  
We reserve the right from time to time to revise this Privacy Policy, so please check this section of our Website periodically for any updates or revisions. If we make any change to this Privacy Policy that materially changes the way we use Information, we will notify you on our Website and you may elect to opt out of such use. We reserve the right to make changes to the Privacy Policy without notice to comply with any law or regulation, court order, or administrative action.

 **Customer service  
**  
To insure that we continue to offer the best customer service possible, we may monitor any of your communications with our employees, whether in writing or by telephone.

 **Contact**

You may telephone us at 1-844-754-8671 or in writing at RK Internet LLC, 4216 Dewitt Avenue, Mattoon, Illinois 61938, Attention: Internet Customer Service
